People be asking me for pictures, man.
And I guess I look fine.
I mean, whatever.
But people take the first opportunity to be like, girl, one girl, I ain't put on no concealer.
And this one lady, I was having a good time on the couch with my friends laughing.
And she said, I see past all your pain in this post.
You've been crying.
You haven't gotten any rest.
You have three nails that have been popped off.
And just look at black women pushing through.
I hate everybody.
I hate people so much.
Girl, I don't have on concealer.
I didn't have the decency to put my nails back on.
Please.
And I'm probably missing one now.
And I'm trying to find it.
No, I hear you.
I hear you.
Because also, people think that their attention to detail is an exemplification of their love for you.
And it's like, but really keep it to yourself.
Yes.
Because I definitely had someone recently look at a picture and be like, hey, sis, love the sandals.
But also, the bunion that's forming on your left foot is something that you should start dealing with right now.
Wow.
Because bunion surgery can be incredible.
Leave me alone.
Bunion surgery is crazy.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.